funenglishgames.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy

The following information explains the privacy policy of the Fun English Games website www.funenglishgames.com.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at funenglishgames@gmail.com. 

The privacy of visitors to www.funenglishgames.com is extremely important to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by www.funenglishgames.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**

Like many other web sites, www.funenglishgames.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies**

www.funenglishgames.com uses cookies to analyze traffic and serve relevant advertising.

**Analytics Cookies**

www.funenglishgames.com uses analytics cookies from Google Analytics. These cookies are used to track how visitors use the www.funenglishgames.com website, including information such as clicks and page views. These cookies are anonymous in that they only identify browsers uniquely, not the people using the browser. 

If you would like to opt-out, a Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on can be found [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

**Advertising Cookies**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.funenglishgames.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.funenglishgames.com and other sites on the Internet. Learn more about how Google uses this information [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites). Further information about online advertising can be found [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) while options for opting-out can be found [here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to display relevant advertisements on www.funenglishgames.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.funenglishgames.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers, our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Google’s privacy policy in relation to advertising can be found [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=en). 

Disabling cookies can also be achieved through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. For further help controlling and disabling cookies, continue reading [here](https://www.cookiesandyou.com/).
